let questions = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "whats your  fname?",
        answer: 'A.my fname is helen.',
        options: [
            "A.my fname is helen.",
            "B.my lname is helen.",
            "C.my favorit color is pink.",
            "D.i'm fine."

        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2,
        question: "The teacher asked if ________ to bring our textbooks to class?",
        answer: 'B.we had all remembered',
        options: [
            "A.all we had remembered",
            "B.we had all remembered",
            "C.had all we remembered",
            "D.had we all remembered"

        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question: "whats your fname?",
        answer: 'A.my fname is helen.',
        options: [
            "A.my fname is helen.",
            "B.my lname is helen.",
            "C.my favorit color is pink.",
            "D.i'm fine."

        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question: "Those apples cost only 1$ _______killo?",
        answer: 'B.a',
        options: [
            "A.for",
            "B.a",
            "C.by",
            "D.the"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 5,
        question: "I have never had a good ….. for learning poems?",
        answer: 'C.memory',
        options: [
            "A.influence",
            "B.knowledge",
            "C.memory",
            "D.report"

        ]
    },
    {
        num: 6,
        question: "Scientists are still …….. into the causes of cancer?",
        answer: 'B.researching',
        options: [
            "A.reporting",
            "B.researching",
            "C.creating",
            "D.caring",
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 7,
        question: "whats your fname?",
        answer: 'A.my fname is helen.',
        options: [
            "A.my fname is helen.",
            "B.my lname is helen.",
            "C.my favorit color is pink.",
            "D.i'm fine."
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 8,
        question: "whats your fname?",
        answer: 'A.my fname is helen.',
        options: [
            "A.my fname is helen.",
            "B.my lname is helen.",
            "C.my favorit color is pink.",
            "D.i'm fine."

        ]
    },
    // {
    //     num: 9,
    //     question: "whats your name?",
    //     answer: 'my name is helen',
    //     options: [

    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     num: 10,
    //     question: "whats your name?",
    //     answer: 'my name is helen',
    //     options: [

    //     ]
    // },

]